Hello.
こんにちは
What are you eating?
何食べてるの?
Shine Muscat.
シャインマスカットです
Do you like it?
好きなの?
I really like it.
めっちゃ好きです
What is it?
なんですけど?
I grew up eating Shine Muscat in Yamanashi.
地元は山梨で シャインマスカットを食べて育ってきました
I'm from Yamanashi.
山梨出身なんだ
山梨出身です
I see.
なるほどね
Did you grow up in Shine Muscat?
シャインマスカットで育ったの?
Most of the body is Shine Muscat?
体の大部分がシャインマスカット?
Yes, it's all Shine Muscat.
そう、全部シャインマスカットです
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's probably amazing.
すごいたぶんね
I don't have a cunt.
おまんない、おゆくた
How old are you now?
今、ゆくつ?
I'm 18 years old now.
今、18歳です
That's right.
そうなんだ
Are you usually a college student?
普段は大学生?
I didn't get into university, so I went back to Yobiko.
大学は落ちちゃったから、 呼び子に帰ってました
Did it fall?
落ちちゃった?
I fell.
落ちちゃった
Does that mean I'm an old man now that I've brought my child home?
呼び子を帰って、老人生ってこと?
Yes, old life.
そう、老人生
Great food.
すごい食べる
That's right.
そうなんだ
I study every day.
毎日勉強だ
I'm studying.
勉強してる
What is your first choice school?
第1志望校はどこなの?
First choice school is Seigaku.
第1志望校は青学
It's Seigaku.
青学なんだ
Seigaku.
青学
Did you want to go to Seigaku even when you were still active?
現役の時も青学に行きたかった?
Yeah.
うん
Why do you want to go to Seigaku?
なんで青学に行きたいの?
Is Seigaku a winner?
青学ってだけで、 勝ち組みかな?
Like.
みたいな
Hey, that's cool.
ねえ、かっこいいもんね
Yeah, that's cool.
うん、かっこいい
Kinda though.
ぽいけどね
Often said.
よく言われる
Are you told?
言われる?
Do you have any dreams for the future?
将来の夢とかあります?
Future dreams?
将来の夢?
dreams of the future
将来の夢は
...
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
For now, I want to enter university.
とりあえず、今は大学に入るために
In order to enter university.
と りあえず大学に入るために
That's great.
えらいね
Where did the call girl go?
呼び子はどこ行ったの?
Yobiko goes to Kawaijuku.
呼び子は、川井塾に行ってます
You're doing it right.
ちゃんとしてるんだね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトはしてないか?
I don't do it now.
今はしてない
Don't you have time?
する時間ないか
He applied.
応募してくれた
What is that?
それは何の?
Taking the exam?
受 験の?
The same goes for taking entrance exams.
受験もそうだし、 受験のダメ
Oh, there's also Shine Muscat.
あ、なんか他、 シャインマスカットないとか
Oh yeah, Shine Muscat because it's expensive.
そうそうそう、高いからシャインマスカット
I see.
なるほどね
I wonder if it's Shine Muscat.
シャインマスカットないかな
It's expensive.
高いもんね
Don't you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏とかはいない?
My boyfriend entered university,
彼氏は、 大学入っちゃって、
We broke up every time.
毎 度別れました
What?
え、何?
My boyfriend?
彼氏が?
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
We dated in high school.
高校に付き合って
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうそう
We dated in high school, then went on to college.
高校に付き合って、 そのまま大学、
My boyfriend got in, but I didn't.
彼氏は入っちゃったけど、 私は入らなかったけど
So, oh, did you leave for a while?
それで、あ、ちょっと離れちゃって?
Yes, I left.
そう、離れちゃって
Well, I was cheated on.
まあ、浮気されました
picture!?
え!?
My boyfriend was cheating on me in college.
彼氏が大学で浮気してた
But that was it.
でも、それかったです
I see.
そっか
But, come on, I won't find a cool boyfriend.
でも、青く入ってさ、 かっこいい彼氏見つけないよ
Find a cool boyfriend.
かっこいい彼氏見つけます
hey!
ね!
blue mountain.
ブルーマウンテン
Blue Mountain?
ブルーマウンテン?
Oh, Blue Mountain?
あ、ブルーマウンテンか
Engesho.
えんげーしょ
Blue soup stock.
青いだし
Ah, certainly.
あ、 確かに
Blue.
青が
picture?
え?
Can I eat too?
俺も食べていい?
You can eat it.
食べていい
Ah, then just a little.
あ、じゃあちょっと
Can I eat it?
食べていい?
Ah, it's coming.
あ、寄ってくる
lol Chemistry.
笑 化学を
Do this?
こうする?
Once.
一回
Is it happening?
なってる?
Properly.
ちゃんと
If you stop by properly.
ちゃんと寄ってくれれば
Great photographer.
素晴らしいカメラマン
get nervous?
緊張する?
get nervous.
緊張する
delicious?
おいしい?
Can I do it too?
俺もやってあげる?
Wait a minute, then.
ちょっと、じゃあ
topping.
トッピング
Because I want the toppings.
トッピングがさ、 欲しいからさ
Just pop this in your mouth and swirl it around.
ちょっと、これ口に ほって、コロコロして
Rolling around.
コロコロ
Kokoro.
コーコロ
Did you get angry?
コーコロした?
Give me the one you're so excited about.
コーコロしたやつを、 俺にください
Like this?
こうやって?
Is it done?
できてる?
Yeah.
うん
Hey, some underwear.
ちょっと、下着をね
I want to play underwear soccer.
下着サッカーやりたいな
下着サッカーやりたいな、みたいな
Have you had sex recently?
最近、エッチした?
I haven't.
してない
Ever since that boyfriend, I've always been softer.
その彼氏以来、 柔らかいのやっぱ
It's different from what I heard.
聞いてた話と違う
Oh, wait a minute.
え、ちょっと待って
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
picture?
え?
Wait, what?
ちょっと、何を?
What were you listening to?
聞いてたのは何?
It's not an underwear shoot.
下着撮影じゃない
Enough already.
もうもうもう
You're not wrong.
間違ってないよ
I'm going to take off my underwear now.
これからさ、下着とるから
What should I do?
どうしていい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
why?
なんで?
Would you like to check my underwear?
ちょっと下着チェックする?
Just give me a license
免許ばっかしてもら
cormorant?
う?
Look at the camera.
カ メラのほう見てごらん
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
difficult.
難しい
Ah, beautiful.
あ、綺麗
There's a stain on my butt.
なんか、お尻がさ、 しみ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
picture?
え?
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Hey, my elbows are so good,
ちょっとさ、肘、 やつうまいなってことで、
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てごらん
It's kind of amazing, but...
なんかさ、 すごいことになってるけど、
Muscat juice is coming out from here.
マスカットの汁が、 ここから出てきてるよ
It's coming out really well.
すーごい出てるじゃん
It's really amazing.
ほ んと、すごい
It's lewd, isn't it?
すけべでしょ
Aren't you stressed out because you have too many licenses?
免許しすぎて、 ストレス溜まってるんじゃない?
Because I haven't done anything yet.
だって、まだ何もしてないよ
It smells really naughty.
すっごいやらしい匂いする
It's a beautiful body.
綺麗な体だね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗じゃん
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
difficult.
難しい
I need a license.
免許しになる
It's soaking wet.
びしょびしょになってるね
It's been a while since someone touched me here.
ここ触られたの、久しぶり
Soaked.
びしょびしょ
Something like that, Ma.
なんかね、 マ
I eat too much scuttle and have body odor.
ス カット食べすぎて、 体臭が
It's pink.
ピンクじゃん
I'm zooming now.
ズームしてる、今